I want to be better than H. Okay.
The last time I sat in a classroom, at the
age of 19, I thought I would
never have to go to school again.  But
now I'm sitting here getting ready
for my first day of school in Vietnam.
I'm also so curious to see how it will be,
because I've been living here for three
months already, but I hardly speak any
Vietnamese.  What should I learn that
I can tell the teacher?
You should be able to introduce yourself.
Ciao.
Z. Ciao.  And then,
and then imagine yourself in front of
the
H
No, I'm not stupid.  That means
I'm stupid today.
J,
what other languages ​​do you speak
besides German?  I also speak a
little English and Japanese, but
my English, for example, has gotten so bad
because I haven't used it at all since school
.  Should I
use bronzer as well?  Yes or no.
Bronze sounds so much like gold.  Bronze.   Say
yes or no.  Say yes or no.  Yes,
I never use bronzer, that's why
you don't know about it.
Unfortunately, it's already broken.  Look, it looks
better, doesn't it?
I see no difference.
He sees no difference.
I'm taking this bag here, a
notebook because she told me to
bring a notebook and a new
Etweet, which is also a
cuddly toy.  Hippo, what do you call
that?  So, this is the finished
makeup.
[laughter] Open up
.   Uh
.  Just call me J Py.  I have it all the
time.  This is my outfit for
the first day of school.  Would you
wear this to a first day of school, or
not?  Now I'm curious to see what
I'll learn in this lesson.  Let's go.
I want to be better than him.
อ
รุย รอ รอ
กาย
อะ อะยุย
Yeah.
Uncle,
you are
thanked. Yes.